Contact

pv8199@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/poojaverma-2613a0179 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Public Speaking Leadership Teamwork

Pooja Verma

Member at IEEE Student and Young professional committee Bombay Section

Durg

Summary

I am a third year undergraduate student of Information technology from Bhilai Institute of Technology , Durg. I am passionate towards gaining knowledge and skills through networking and reading as well as has a good experience in team work

Experience

IEEE Student and Young professional committee Bombay Section Member June 2020 - Present (3 months)

` '

IEEE Women in Engineering Member

March 2020 - Present (6 months)

IEEE BIT DURG

1 year 10 months

Chairperson

January 2020 - Present (8 months)

Durg Area, India

Volunteer

November 2018 - Present (1 year 10 months)

Durg Area, India

Secretary

April 2019 - September 2019 (6 months)

The Astro Club

3 years 1 month

Member

August 2017 - Present (3 years 1 month)

Durg Area, India

As a member of astro club we participated in various telescopic sessions, messier marathons and expert lecture talks.

Head Of Research And Development August 2019 - August 2020 (1 year 1 month) Durg Area, India

member of content committee August 2018 - August 2019 (1 year 1 month) Durg Area, India

My main role as a member of the content committee was to provide content to the whole team regarding the upcoming events and report writing for the same.

Education

Bhilai Institute of Technology (BIT), Durg
BE - Bachelor of Engineering, Information Technology · (2017 - 2021)